

PERSONAL SKILLS

- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript
- GIT
- Google Chrome developer tools
- Writing bug reports, checklists and test plans
- Adobe Photoshop / Figma
- Adaptive and cross-browser layout
- SEO
- Writing technical specifications
- Trello / Jira / Slack
- Google Analytics / Ads
- SMM

SOFT SKILLS

- Control of team work
- Team motivation
- Generate weekly / monthly reports
- Multitasking
- Problem solving
- Fast response
- Delegation of tasks
- Fast learner
- Analytical and critical thinking

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English (Intermediate / B1)
- Russian (Advanced / C1)
- Ukrainian (Proficiency / C2)

CONTSCTS:





<u>Telegram</u>

Instagram

Linkedin

€ Portfolio

Dmitry Lobachevsky

Junior Project Manager

Kyiv, Ukraine | 25 y.o.

750\$

ABOUT ME:

Hey!

My name is Dmitry, I am the Project Manager.

I started learning HTML / CSS through video tutorials and online courses.

I got most of my knowledge from self-education and practical experience.

In the last places of work, I held the position of PM, my team consisted of 6+ people.

My experience as a project manager is 1+ year.

I always try to develop and improve my skills. I am looking for interesting projects and is open to any cooperation and communication.

Why Project Manager?

Because I enjoy my work, creating cool projects and leading the team!

WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Control Manager / Project Manager

EVERAD

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

- Setting goals
- Monitoring team work and completing tasks on time
- Quality control of products in accordance with technical documentation
- Preparation of reports for a week / month

Webmaster

UAMADE STORE

OCT 2019 - JUL 2021

- Adaptive and cross-browser layout
- Layout on CMS
- Administrative support for 3 sites
- Making SEO edits
- Filling the site with content
- Writing technical specifications
- Testing of web products.
- Writing bug reports, checklists and test cases
- Setting tasks for programmers, content maker, SEO and work control
- Promotion and collection of analytics

Restaurant manager

TENNESSEE RESTAURANT JUN 2019 - SEP 2019

- Control of staff work
- Resolving conflict situations
- Registration of supplies
- Restaurant Proceedings Report
- Interviewing candidates



PERSONAL SKILLS

- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript
- GIT
- Google Chrome developer tools
- Writing bug reports, checklists and test plans
- Adobe Photoshop / Figma
- Adaptive and cross-browser layout
- SEO
- Writing technical specifications
- Trello / Jira / Slack
- Google Analytics / Ads
- SMM

SOFT SKILLS

- Control of team work
- Team motivation
- Generate weekly / monthly reports
- Multitasking
- Problem solving
- Fast response
- Delegation of tasks
- Fast learner
- Analytical and critical thinking

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English (Intermediate / B1)
- Russian (Advanced / C1)
- Ukrainian (Proficiency / C2)

CONTSCTS:



+380 (99) 463 41 39



dmitryielail@gmail.com



<u>Telegram</u>



O Instagram





EDUCATION

Ucode

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Year of completion 2021

National University of Food Technologies (Kiev)
BACHELOR OF HOTEL AND RESTAURANT BUSINESS
Year of completion 2018

College of Economics and Law (Kiev)
CATERING BUSINESS

Year of completion 2015

CONTACT US FOR A RECOMMENDATION

Yaroslav Kozik EVERAD

+380(96)177-26-56

Τx